

CONTACT

+41 766 194 431

nathalie.persson@hotmail.com

Verbier, Switzerland

SKILLS

Programming LanguagesJavaScript, TypeScript, HTML, CSS/Sass

Libraries & FrameworksReact, Angular, Node.js, Express

Tools & Platforms Github, Figma, Wordpress, Netlify, Heroku

Design Illustrator, Photoshop

Languages
Swedish. Native
English. Fluent
French. Intermediate

INTERESTS

Skiing, hiking, cooking, movies, reading, traveling and yoga

Nathalie Jane

Persson Enriquez FRONTEND DEVELOPER

Happy and social 28 year old from Gothenburg, Sweden. Moved to Switzerland, Verbier 6 years ago to enjoy the nature and the mountains.

Previously worked in the Restaurant Industry for 9 years. Now studying what I've always wanted to do - coding.

EXPERIENCE

RESTAURANT MANAGER

SHED RESTAURANTS 2016 - 2021 // Verbier, Switzerland

Busy gourmet burger restaurant. Oversaw hiring process and interviews. Supervising and training up to 15 employees. Digitalized schedule planning, time-clocking, orders and inventory. With apps such as 75hifts and Backbar.

BREAKFAST MANAGER / CONFERENCE HOST NOVOTEL

2013 - 2021 // Gothenburg, Sweden

4-star hotel by the sea. Started as waitress, promoted to breakfast manager and later on conference host. Prepared breakfast for up to 500 people. Supervising and training staff. Managing conferences for up to 200 people.

EDUCATION

FRONTEND DEVELOPMENT
MEDIEINSTITUET
2021 - 2023 // Stockholm, Sweden (Remote)

Studying remotely with following courses -HTML/CSS, JavaScript, API-development, Agile Project Managment, Entrepreneurship, Graphic Tools for UI and UX.

ECONOMICS PROGRAM SJÖLINS GYMNASIUM 2010 - 2013 // Gothenburg, Sweden